Contexts = [
    { # 1030
        "Question": "What are the symptoms of tachycardia? 心跳過速有哪些症狀？",   
        "Evidence": ["1. No matter which type of tachycardia you have, you may feel: Dizziness Lightheadedness Shortness of breath Chest pain Heart palpitations In extreme cases, you could become unconscious or go into cardiac arrest. 無論您患有哪種類型的心動過速，您都可能會感到： 頭暈 頭暈 呼吸短促 胸痛 心悸 在極端情況下，您可能會失去知覺或心臟驟停。",
                     "2. But sometimes, a super-fast heart rate causes no symptoms at all. 但有時，超快的心率根本不會引起任何症狀。"],
        "Answer": "Symptoms of tachycardia may include dizziness, lightheadedness, shortness of breath, chest pain, heart palpitations, and in extreme cases, unconsciousness or cardiac arrest. However, sometimes a super-fast heart rate causes no symptoms at all. 心搏過速的症狀可能包括頭暈、頭暈、氣短、胸痛、心悸，在極端情況下，甚至會出現意識不清或心臟停止。然而，有時超快的心率根本不會引起任何症狀。"
    },
    { # 1008
        "Question": "How can pets cause allergy problems in bedrooms? 寵物如何在臥室引起過敏問題？",
        "Evidence": ["1. But dander, saliva, and pee from furry animals can carry allergens. 但毛茸茸的動物的皮屑、唾液和尿液可能帶有過敏原。",
                     "2. Ideally, your dog or cat should sleep somewhere else. 理想情況下，您的狗或貓應該睡在其他地方。",
                     "3. If not, do your best to reduce dander. 如果沒有，請盡力減少皮屑。",
                     "4. For example, vacuum more often. 例如，更頻繁地吸塵。"],
        "Answer": "Pets can cause allergy problems in bedrooms because their dander, saliva, and pee can carry allergens. Ideally, pets should sleep in a different room. If this is not possible, try to reduce dander by vacuuming more often. 寵物在臥室可能會引起過敏問題，因為它們的皮屑、唾液和尿液可能帶有過敏原。理想情況下，寵物應該睡在不同的房間。如果無法做到這一點，請嘗試更頻繁地吸塵以減少皮屑。"
    },
    { # 0
        "Question":"Can you get a test for swine flu? 您可以進行豬流感檢測嗎？",
        "Evidence": ["1: If you have swine flu, you may be more likely to feel sick and your stomach and throw up than with regular flu.如果您患有豬流感，與普通流感相比，您可能更容易感到噁心、胃部不適和嘔吐。",
                     "2: Antibiotics won't do anything for you. 抗生素對您沒有任何作用。"],
        "Answer": "Swine flu can cause stomach upset and vomiting, and antibiotics are ineffective against it. 豬流感會引起胃部不適和嘔吐，而抗生素對此無效。"
    },
    { # 3
        "Question": "How is tongue cancer prevented? 如何預防舌癌？",
        "Evidence": ["1: We know that many cases of base-of-the-tongue cancer are caused by HPV. 我們知道許多舌根癌病例是由 HPV 引起的。",
                     "2: Some things that may make you less likely to get this type of cancer are: If you're not sexually active, get vaccinated for HPV. \
                        一些可能降低您罹患此類癌症的可能性的因素包括： 如果您性生活不活躍，請接種 HPV 疫苗。",
                    "3: If you are sexually active, use latex condoms every time you have sex. 如果您性生活活躍，每次發生性行為時都使用乳膠保險套。",
                    "4: Don't use tobacco in any form.不要使用任何形式的菸草。",
                    "5: Avoid heavy or frequent alcohol use. 避免大量或頻繁飲酒。",
                    "6: Take good care of your teeth and gums.照顧好牙齒和牙齦。"],
        "Answer": "HPV vaccination, latex condoms, no tobacco, no alcohol, good oral hygiene can help prevent tongue cancer.\
            HPV疫苗接種、乳膠保險套、戒菸戒酒、良好的口腔衛生有助於預防舌癌。"
    },
    { # 10
        "Question": "Can I drink alcohol if I have diabetic nerve pain? 如果我有糖尿病神經痛，我可以喝酒嗎？",
        "Evidence": [ "1: Pain often disrupts sleep. 疼痛常常擾亂睡眠。",
                     "2: So does alcohol. 酒精也是如此。"],
        "Answer": "Alcohol and pain can both disrupt sleep. 酒精和疼痛都會擾亂睡眠。"
    },
    { # 1035
        "Question": "How can you treat symptoms of de Quervain's disease? 如何治療奎文氏症的症狀？",
        "Evidence": [ "1. You'll start with over-the-counter pain relievers like ibuprofen or naproxen to ease the swelling. 你可以先使用布洛芬或萘普生等非處方止痛藥來緩解腫脹。",
                      "2. But try these methods at home to feel better and keep your thumb healthy: Ice the area to ease inflammation. 但是在家嘗試這些方法可以感覺更好並保持拇指健康：冰敷該區域以緩解發炎。"],
        "Answer": "Over-the-counter pain relievers like ibuprofen or naproxen can be used to ease the swelling, and icing the area can help to reduce inflammation. 布洛芬或萘普生等非處方止痛藥可用於緩解腫脹，冰敷患處有助於減輕發炎。"
    },
    { # 1037
        "Question": "What is pembrolizumab (Keytruda) for treating small-cell lung cancer (SCLC)? 什麼是派姆單抗（Keytruda）用於治療小細胞肺癌（SCLC）？",
        "Evidence": [ "1. You might take this immune checkpoint inhibitor along with chemotherapy. 您可以將這種免疫檢查點抑制劑與化療一起服用。",
                      "2. Your doctor will decide how long you'll get this medication. 您的醫生將決定您服用這種藥物的時間。"],
        "Answer": "Pembrolizumab (Keytruda) is an immune checkpoint inhibitor that may be used in combination with chemotherapy to treat small-cell lung cancer (SCLC). Your doctor will determine how long you will receive this medication. \
            Pembrolizumab (Keytruda) 是一種免疫檢查點抑制劑，可與化療聯合用於治療小細胞肺癌 (SCLC)。您的醫生將確定您將接受這種藥物多長時間。"
    },
    { # 4008
        "Question": "What should I do if my medications cause dry eye? 如果我的藥物導致乾眼症，我該怎麼辦？",
        "Evidence": [ "1. Instead, talk to your doctor about it. 相反，請與您的醫生討論此事。",
                      "2. You may be able to: Change the dose of your medication.您也許能夠： 改變藥物劑量。",
                      "3. Switch to a different medicine that doesn't cause dry eye.改用另一種不會引起乾眼症的藥物。",
                    "4. Try different contacts.嘗試不同的隱形眼鏡。"
                    "5. Use artificial tears to keep your eyes moist. 使用人工淚液保持眼睛濕潤。"],
        "Answer": "If your medications cause dry eye, talk to your doctor about it. \
            You may be able to change the dose of your medication, switch to a different medicine that doesn't cause dry eye, try different contacts, \
                or use artificial tears to keep your eyes moist.  \
                如果您的藥物導致乾眼症，請諮詢您的醫生。 \
                您可以改變藥物劑量、改用不會引起乾眼症的其他藥物、嘗試不同的隱形眼鏡或使用人工淚液保持眼睛濕潤。"
    },
    { # 413
        "Question": "When is the best time to eat after working out if I have diabetes? 如果我患有糖尿病，運動後什麼時候吃東西最好？",
        "Evidence": [ "1. Even if you don't need a snack right after you work out, you'll still need to build your energy back to help your muscles recover. 即使您運動後不需要立即吃零食，您仍然需要恢復能量以幫助肌肉恢復。",
                      "2. The best time to eat is between 30 minutes and 2 hours after you're done. 最佳進食時間是飯後 30 分鐘到 2 小時。"],
        "Answer": "Individuals with diabetes should eat a snack or meal within 30 minutes to 2 hours after working out to help build energy and aid in muscle recovery. 糖尿病患者應在運動後 30 分鐘至 2 小時內吃點零食或正餐，以幫助補充能量並幫助肌肉恢復。"
    },
    { 
        # 13
        "Question": "How do lower cholesterol levels increase the chance of getting type 2 diabetes? 較低的膽固醇水平如何增加患第 2 型糖尿病的機會？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1: Your \"good\" cholesterol level is low. 您的「好」膽固醇水平較低。",
            "2: It's too low if it's less than 40 mg/dL (milligrams per deciliter). 如果低於 40 mg/d L（毫克每分升），表示含量太低。"
            ],
        "Answer": "Low levels of \"good\" cholesterol (high-density lipoprotein, or HDL) increase the risk of type 2 diabetes. HDL levels below 40 mg/dL are considered low. 低水平的「好」膽固醇（高密度脂蛋白，或 HDL）會增加罹患第 2 型糖尿病的風險。 HDL 水準低於 40 mg/dL 被認為是低水準。"
    },
    { 
        # 1017,
        "Question": "Why shouldn't you smoke when you're sick? 為什麼生病時不應該抽煙？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. Smoking damages your lungs and irritates your throat. 吸煙會損害肺部並刺激喉嚨。",
            "2. That can make your cold symptoms worse. 這會讓你的感冒症狀變得更糟。",
            "3. So ditch the cigarettes and steer clear of secondhand smoke. 因此，戒掉香煙並遠離二手煙。"
        ],
        "Answer": "Smoking can worsen cold symptoms by damaging your lungs and irritating your throat. It is important to avoid cigarettes and secondhand smoke when you are sick. 吸煙會損害肺部並刺激喉嚨，從而加重感冒症狀。生病時避免吸煙和二手煙非常重要。"
    },
    { 
        # 425,
        "Question": "What is recovery like for an ankle sprain or fracture? 腳踝扭傷或骨折的恢復情況如何？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. It could be a sprain, or it might be broken. 可能是扭傷，也可能是骨折。",
            "2. Most sprains will clear up on their own. 大多數扭傷會自行消失。",
            "3. You should start range of motion exercises once the pain and swelling subside. 一旦疼痛和腫脹消退，您就應該開始進行活動範圍練習。"
        ],
        "Answer": "An ankle sprain or fracture can be difficult to distinguish, but most sprains will heal on their own. Once the pain and swelling subside, you should begin range of motion exercises to help restore mobility to your ankle. 腳踝扭傷或骨折可能很難區分，但大多數扭傷會自行癒合。一旦疼痛和腫脹消退，您應該開始進行活動範圍練習，以幫助恢復腳踝的活動能力。"
    },
    { 
        # 1016,
        "Question": "Is it OK to do things besides sleep in your bedroom when you have insomnia? 失眠時可以在臥室裡做除了睡覺以外的事嗎？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. If you suffer from insomnia, do not balance the checkbook, study, or make phone calls, for example, while in bed or even in the bedroom, and avoid watching television or listening to the radio. 如果您患有失眠症，請勿在床上甚至臥室內平衡支票簿、學習或打電話，並避免看電視或聽廣播。",
            "2. All these activities can increase alertness and make it difficult to fall asleep. 所有這些活動都會提高警覺性並導致入睡困難。",
            "3. Your bed should feel comfortable and if you have a pet that sleeps in the room with you, consider having the pet sleep somewhere else if it tends to make noise in the night. 您的床應該感覺舒適，如果您有寵物與您一起睡在房間裡，如果寵物在夜間容易發出噪音，請考慮讓寵物睡在其他地方。"
        ],
        "Answer": "Individuals with insomnia should avoid doing activities in the bedroom that increase alertness, such as balancing the checkbook, studying, or making phone calls. Additionally, watching television or listening to the radio in the bedroom should be avoided. The bed should be a place for rest and comfort, and if a pet sleeps in the bedroom with the individual, it may be helpful to have the pet sleep elsewhere if it tends to make noise at night. 失眠患者應避免在臥室進行會提高警覺性的活動，例如平衡支票簿、學習或打電話。此外，應避免在臥室看電視或聽廣播。床應該是一個休息和舒適的地方，如果寵物與人一起睡在臥室裡，如果寵物在晚上容易發出噪音，那麼讓寵物睡在別處可能會有所幫助。"
    },
    { 
        # 439,
        "Question": "What are complications of heart failure that can affect your sleep? 心臟衰竭的哪些併發症會影響您的睡眠？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. For example: Chest pain and discomfort make it hard to relax and fall or stay asleep. 例如： 胸痛和不適使人難以放鬆、入睡或入睡。",
            "2. Lying in bed can make you feel short of breath. 躺在床上會讓您感到呼吸急促。",
            "3. You may have to get up during the night to pee. 您可能需要在夜間起床小便。"
        ],
        "Answer": "Heart failure can cause complications that can make it difficult to sleep, such as chest pain, shortness of breath, and needing to get up during the night to urinate. 心臟衰竭會導致難以入睡的併發症，例如胸痛、呼吸急促以及需要在夜間起床小便。"
    },
    { 
        # 49,
        "Question": "What are my risks if I have multiple sclerosis and sleep apnea? 如果我患有多發性硬化症和睡眠呼吸暫停，我會面臨哪些風險？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. Sleep apnea can do more than make you feel tired during the day. 睡眠呼吸中止症不僅會讓您在白天感到疲倦。",
            "2. If you don't treat it, it can increase your risk for the following: Accidents, such as car accidents Diabetes Heart attack Heart failure High blood pressure Irregular heartbeat Obesity Stroke It can also affect your memory and make it harder for you to think clearly. 如果您不治療，可能會增加以下風險： 事故，例如車禍 糖尿病 心臟病 心臟衰竭 高血壓 心跳不規律 肥胖 中風 它還會影響您的記憶力，使您難以記憶想清楚。"
        ],
        "Answer": "If you have multiple sclerosis and sleep apnea, you are at an increased risk for accidents, diabetes, heart attack, heart failure, high blood pressure, irregular heartbeat, obesity, stroke, memory problems, and difficulty thinking clearly. 如果您患有多發性硬化症和睡眠呼吸暫停，您發生事故、糖尿病、心臟病、心臟衰竭、高血壓、心律不整、肥胖、中風、記憶問題和清晰思考困難的風險就會增加。"
    },
    { 
        # 470,
        "Question": "How can a white board help me stay organized? 白板如何幫助我保持井然有序？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. Put one on your fridge or other area where you spend a lot of time. 將一個放在冰箱或其他您經常待的地方。",
            "2. Write notes and to-do lists on it. 在上面寫下筆記和待辦事項清單。"
        ],
        "Answer": "To stay organized, you can use a white board by placing it in a location where you spend a lot of time, such as on your fridge. You can then write notes and to-do lists on the board to help you keep track of your tasks. \
            為了保持井井有條，您可以將白板放置在您經常使用的位置（例如冰箱上）。然後，您可以在板上寫下筆記和待辦事項列表，以幫助您追蹤任務。"
    },
    { 
        # 2028,
        "Question": "How can you tell if pain around your groin is caused by prostatitis? 如何判斷腹股溝周圍的疼痛是否由攝護腺炎引起？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. Prostatitis: This is swelling or infection in your prostate gland. 攝護腺炎：這是攝護腺腫脹或感染。",
            "2. In addition to pain, you may have a hard time peeing. 除了疼痛之外，您可能還難以排尿。"
        ],
        "Answer": "Pain around the groin can be caused by prostatitis, which is swelling or infection in the prostate gland. In addition to pain, you may also have difficulty urinating. 腹股溝周圍的疼痛可能是由前列腺炎引起的，前列腺炎是前列腺腫脹或感染。除了疼痛之外，您還可能會出現排尿困難。"
    },
    { 
        # 87,
        "Question": "How can a hysterectomy help with a heavy period? 子宮切除術如何幫助緩解月經過多？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. In extreme cases, you may need this surgery, which will remove your uterus. 在極端情況下，您可能需要進行手術，切除子宮。",
            "2. You won't get your period anymore, but you also won't be able to get pregnant. 您將不再來月經，但也將無法懷孕。"
        ],
        "Answer": "Hysterectomy is a surgery that removes the uterus. It can be used to treat heavy periods. After a hysterectomy, you will no longer have periods, but you will also not be able to get pregnant. 子宮切除術是一種切除子宮的手術。它可以用來治療月經過多。子宮切除術後，您將不再有月經，但也將無法懷孕。"
    },
    { 
        # 411,
        "Question": "What causes Bowen's disease other than HPV? 除了 HPV 之外，還有什麼原因導致鮑文氏症？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. Scientists aren't sure exactly what causes the other forms of Bowen's disease. 科學家不確定是什麼原因導致其他形式的鮑文氏病。",
            "2. However, long-term sun exposure and aging may increase your odds of getting many skin cancers, including this one. 然而，長期暴露在陽光下和衰老可能會增加患多種皮膚癌的幾率，包括這種皮膚癌。",
            "3. Poisoning with arsenic also appears to make you more likely to get this early form of skin cancer. 砷中毒也會增加皮膚癌的風險。"
        ],
        "Answer": "Although scientists are not certain what causes Bowen's disease, long-term sun exposure, aging, and arsenic poisoning are all known to increase the risk of developing this type of skin cancer. 儘管科學家不確定是什麼原因導致鮑文氏症，但長期暴露在陽光下、老化和砷中毒都會增加這種皮膚癌的風險。"
    },
    { 
        # 437,
        "Question": "What types of therapy can help kids with autism communicate better? 哪些類型的治療可以幫助自閉症兒童更好溝通？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. They find it hard to make eye contact. 他們發現很難進行目光接觸。",
            "2. Younger kids start with behavior therapy, and the doctor may prescribe medication if symptoms don't improve enough. 年幼的孩子開始接受行為治療，如果症狀改善不夠，醫生可能會開藥。"
        ],
        "Answer": "Younger children with autism may benefit from behavioral therapy, and medication may be prescribed if symptoms do not improve. 年幼的自閉症兒童可能會受益於行為治療，如果症狀沒有改善，可能會開藥。"
    },
    { 
        # 2008,
        "Question": "Is there a link between poorly managed diabetes and erectile dysfunction (ED)? 糖尿病管理不善與勃起功能障礙 (ED) 之間是否存在關聯？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. Poorly managed diabetes : Diabetes can affect blood flow to your penis. 糖尿病管理不善：糖尿病會影響陰莖的血液流動。",
            "2. Maintain a healthy diet, get regular exercise, and take your medicine as prescribed. 保持健康的飲食，定期鍛煉，並按處方服藥。"
        ],
        "Answer": "Poorly managed diabetes can affect blood flow to the penis, leading to erectile dysfunction. Maintaining a healthy diet, getting regular exercise, and taking medication as prescribed can help to improve blood flow and reduce the risk of ED. 糖尿病管理不善會影響陰莖的血液流動，導致勃起功能障礙。保持健康的飲食、定期運動和按處方服藥有助於改善血液流動並降低 ED 的風險。"
    },
    { 
        # 430,
        "Question": "How can taking it easy help with sexual performance anxiety? 放鬆如何幫助緩解性表現焦慮？",
        "Evidence": [
            "1. Don't beat yourself up about your appearance or ability in bed. 不要因為自己的外表或床上能力而自責。",
            "2. Get help for sexual performance anxiety so you can get back to having a healthy and enjoyable sex life. 獲得有關性表現焦慮的幫助，這樣您就可以恢復健康、愉快的性生活。"
        ],
        "Answer": "To avoid sexual performance anxiety, do not be hard on yourself about your appearance or ability in bed, and seek professional help if needed. 為了避免性表現焦慮，不要對自己的外表或床上能力太苛刻，並在需要時尋求專業協助。"
    }
]

questions = [
    {
        "text": "Question 1: 答案(Answer)是否只包含證據(Evidence)中提到的資訊? (亦即是否有超出證據的資訊)",
        "options": ["1: 完全符合", "2: 大部分符合", "3: 少部分符合", "4: 完全不符合"],
        "options_note": ["完全符合 (答案完全依循證據中的資訊，沒有任何超出證據的額外資訊。換言之，答案提及的資訊都可以在證據中找到)。\
                         [補充: 這包含用詞不同但意義上相同的答案，或者為了使回答更流暢而加入的詞句並不算超出證據]",
                         "大部分符合 (答案大部分依循證據中的資訊，但可能加入了一些輔助資訊或解釋。\
                            這些輔助資訊並不改變證據的主要含義，但可能增加了一些背景或細節，並且這些細節是正確的。)",
                         "部分符合 (答案只有部分根據證據中的資訊，其他大部分內容是由 LLM 加入的額外資訊或解釋，這些資訊可能是證據的延伸或無關，\
                            但無法保證這些延伸的正確性)",
                         "完全不符合 (答案完全沒有根據證據中的資訊，內容都是額外資訊、錯誤資訊或與證據無關的內容。)"]
    },
    {
        "text": "Question 2: 答案(Answer)是否涵蓋所有證據(Evidence)中提及的資訊?",
        "options": ["1: 完全涵蓋","2: 大部分涵蓋","3: 部分涵蓋", "4: 完全未涵蓋"],
        "options_note": ["完全涵蓋 (答案的內容涵蓋了證據中每個提及的重要資訊，這些資訊在答案中可能經過重寫、精簡、總結，但意思不變。)",
                            "大部分涵蓋 (答案內容涵蓋證據中的大部分片段的重要資訊，\
                                但可能有些未包含，其中未包含的片段為可省略的次要或無關資訊。)",
                            "部分涵蓋 (答案中只有一部分重要資訊被涵蓋，大部分證據片段並未在答案被提及，代表有重要的片段被忽略了。)",
                            "完全未涵蓋 (答案中完全沒有涵蓋證據中的任何句子所提及的重要資訊。)"]
    },
    {
        "text": "Question 3: 答案(Answer)的表達是否通順且流利?",
        "options": ["1: 非常通順","2: 較為通順","3: 不太通順", "4: 非常不通順"],
        "options_note": ["非常通順 (答案表達流暢、通順。)",
                            "較為通順 (答案表達大致流暢，但可能有少量語法錯誤或不自然的表達方式，但不影響整體理解。)",
                            "不太通順 (答案表達不太流暢，有較多的語法錯誤或不自然的地方，影響了理解。)",
                            "非常不通順 (答案表達不流暢，具有語法錯誤與不自然的表達，難以理解。)"]
    },
    {
        "text": "Question 4: 答案 (Answer) 的內容是否正確?",
        "options": ["1: 完全正確","2: 大部分正確","3: 部分正確", "4: 完全不正確"],
        "options_note": ["完全正確 (獨立於其他題目，假設Evidence為Ground truth (正解) 的情況下，答案中的資訊正確，與證據或已知事實一致。或者基於你的知識背景，答案中的資訊是正確的。)",
                         "大部分正確 (獨立於其他題目，假設Evidence為Ground truth (正解) 的情況下，答案中的大部分資訊是正確的，但可能有一些小錯誤或不準確的地方。)",
                         "部分正確 (獨立於其他題目，假設Evidence為Ground truth (正解) 的情況下，答案中只有一部分資訊是正確的，大部分內容有誤。)",
                         "完全不正確 (獨立於其他題目，假設Evidence為Ground truth (正解) 的情況下，答案中的所有資訊都是錯誤的，沒有一部分是正確的。)"]
    }
]

def get_contexts():
    return Contexts

def get_questions():
    return questions
